It's a bit dangerous to be a cram school teacher...
ちょっと塾の先生でやってやばいよ...
But once every five years, you have to study, dressed like this...
でも5年一度は勉強さ、こういう格好をして...
Um...the girls class I'm doing...
あの...やってる女子授業...
It makes me horny...
ムラムラするよね...
Is it gone?
しまった?
Are you seducing me?
誘惑するの?
Not at all...
全然全然全然...
Now Oppa...
これでさ、オッパーがさ...
This is why I taught you this right next to you, right?
これがさ、横でこうやって教えた訳でしょ?
Were you pushing your oppa?
オッパーを押し付けてきてたの?
No, I won't...
いや、私からはしないよ...
What do you mean by me?
私からはどういうこと?
I won't do it, but...
私からはしないけど...
I'll hit it...
当たっちゃう...
How did you do it?
どうやった?
Try it...
やってみて...
You're doing it!
やっててんじゃん!
different...
違う...
You're doing it...
やっててんじゃん...
Do it...
やってやって...
I'll hit it...
当たっちゃう...
You're doing it!
やってんじゃん!
Because it's close...
近いから...
Like this... how do you get this close?
こうやって...こんな密着するの?
Yeah...
うん...
With the teacher?
先生と?
Yeah...
うん...
Moreover, the teacher's dick is getting hard...
しかも先生のチンコは固くなっていく...
a little bit ...
ちょっと ...
Not that Kepi...
そのケピさんじゃねえ...
Ikemeika...
イケメイカ...
Eh, but quite...
え、でも結構...
So, are you going with 100 people?
じゃあ 100人とか行ってるの?
I haven't gone, I haven't gone...
行ってない行ってない...
10 people...we have to go...
10人...行かないと...
10 people have to go...
10人行かないと...
Quite a lot, but still...
結構多いけどな、それでも...
I thought you were 18 years old...
18歳だなって思ったけどね...
Was it your first time?
初めてしたの?
when?
いつ?
Little 6...
小6...
Hurry!
早っ!
That's a lie!
嘘でしょ!
How old were you?
何歳だったっけ?
that...
それ...
Little 6...
小6...
Like 12 years old?
12歳とか?
Yeah ...
うん ...
Eh, then you can't do it?
え、じゃあできへんの?
Yeah...
うん...
Who did you do it with?
誰としたの?
Jek person...
ジェクの人...
Jake's friend?
ジェクの友達?
The teacher I was born with...
生まれがとの先生...
gentlemen!?
先生!?
How old are you?
何歳?
university student...
大学生...
Eh, you're an Oricon guy...
え、オリコン野郎じゃん...
Yeah...
うん...
Huh, didn't it hurt?
え、痛くなかった?
If you enter...
入ったらちんちん...
Yeah
うん
...
Oh, wow...
あ、 すっごい...
Huge...
でっか...
terrible...
やばい...
terrible?
やばい?
Yeah...
うん...
Have you ever heard your voice when you were not 12 years old?
12歳以外の時の声、おっぱう聞かれた?
Yeah...like D...
うん...Dとかの...
Seriously!?
マジで!?
You're an adult...
大人だね...
Well, let's do this once...
え、今これを一回さ...
Ha, old man
は、じい
...
Hey, let's go right away...
ちょっと さっそくじゃあさ...
Too lewd...
すけべしたぎ...
picture?
え?
Hey, it's okay...
ちょ、いいのにして...
what?
何?
This lewd...
このすけべしたぎ...
picture?
え?
She's really cute though...
め っちゃ可愛いんだけど...
Asuka Kira...
アスカキラ...
アスカキラの...
brand...
ブランド...
Is Asuka Kira a brand?
アスカキラがブランドなの?
Look... look...
もうだって...見て、こば...
Koba...
こば...
I can't get into it anymore...
もう...入りきれないくなってるよ、
this...
これ...
Look, look...
ほ ら、ほら...
Eh, this is a school uniform, right?
え、これさ、学校制服でしょ?
Are you going to wear something like this?
これ、こういうのつけるの?
Yeah...
うん...
Are you going to school like this?
学校これで行ってんの?
no way...
とんでもない...
It's a woman
女だね
...
You drank a lot, didn't you?
い っぱい飲んでしょ、これ...
School provider...
学 校提供士か...
Are you drinking a lot?
いっぱい飲んでる?
That was bad
下手だったね
...
It's heavy, after all.
重 いね、やっぱね
...
Touch it yourself
自 分で触ったりさ
...
why?
なん で?
なんで?
Embarrassing...
恥ずかしい...
Usually, it's better to be touched...
だいたい、触られる方が...
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
It's cute...
可愛いです...
I want to take a good look
よく見たい
...
Even though I'm thin...
痩 せてるのにさ...
It's that big, isn't it?
そんなでかいですよね
...
Erotic...
エ ロい...
Erotic...I don't know
エロい...知らない
...
That's not what I mean...
そう いうわけじゃない...
Looks like a meat bun...
肉まんみたい...
I really like this
これ、すげえ好きなんだね
...
That...
それ さ...
Well, stand up.
じゃあ、立ってさ
...
You look thin...
痩 せてるね...
I'm thin
痩せてる
...
amazing...
すごい...
Sweet
甘くて
...
Hey, I don't drink...
ちょ い、飲まない...
don't drink
飲まない
...
Just a little bit more
もう ちょい
...
can't drink
飲 めない
...
a little bit...
ちょっと...
a little bit ...
ちょっと ...
It's soaking wet...
びしょびしょだ...
Soaked...
びしょびしょ...
It's soaking wet...
びしょびしょになってる...
Even if I lie down?
寝座しても?
Seriously?
マジ?
Even if I lie down?
寝座しても?
lie down
寝座して
too?
も?
why?
なん で?
なんで?
Various things
いろんなさ
...
Can you even touch the one that came out?
出 たやつ、ちょっと触っても?